https://www.mymysteryparty.com/privacy-policy/

Home
Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Our Commitment To Your PrivacyYour privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy the following notice explains the information we collect, how it is used, how it is safeguarded, and how to contact us if you have any concerns.What Information Is Collected:As part of the order process, the following information is collected from shoppers:Name Shipping/Billing Address Email address Phone number Credit/Debit Card InformationHow That Information Is Used:The information that we collect is used such as to complete your order, to contact you if we have questions, or to send you an email with special offers.Information securityWe take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.We restrict access to personal information to mymysteryparty.com employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.Data integrityMymysteryparty.com processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.Our Commitment To The Security of Your DataMymysteryparty.com may disclose your data, the contents of your private communications, or the contact information of your guests if required to do so by law, or as otherwise stated in this policy, or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (1) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on mymysteryparty.com; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of mymysteryparty.com; or (3) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of its members or the public. Also, certain technical processing of e-mail messages and their content may be required to: (1) send and receive messages; (2) conform to connecting networks' technical requirements; (3) conform to the limitations of the Service; or (4) conform to other similar requirements.It is possible that as we continue to develop our Web site and our business, mymysteryparty.com and/or related assets might be acquired. In such a transaction, customer information may be transferred to the acquiring entity.Changes to this policyPlease note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Policy changes). Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.
Categories
Murder Mystery Parties
Virtual Mystery Parties
Catch a Killer Games
Adult Mystery Parties
Teen Mystery Parties
Kid's Mystery Parties
Non Murder
Frequently Asked Questions (FAQ)
All prices are in USD.
© 2020 My Mystery Party
Sitemap |
Loading... Please wait...
×
×
